<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Task 8
    </string>

    <string name="first_text">Man is a social being. He lives in society. As a gregarious and
        social being he lives and interacts with so many people all through his life.

        In our interactions with people we make many friends. We enjoy the company of our friends;
        in fact that is why they are our friends.

        We influence our friends, and likewise our friends influence us. Friendships therefore have
        a great bearing on our life. That is why we must be choosy when we make friends, because
        we want long lasting true friends whom we may trust and who, in turn, can trust us.
        Friendship calls for loyalty. If you cannot be loyal to your friends, you will lose them.

        In a real friendship that has matured over time, there are not even any expectations
        between two friends. You love your friend whatever may happen, and you love not for any
        reason or to get anything in return from your friend. And this is the sentiment shared by
        your friend too. Such a friendship is a real friendship and it gives true joy and
        contentment. Even troubles and miseries that life may bring seem insignificant when you have
        such a friendship to bank on.
    </string>

    <string name="second_text">Friendship is a bond that is built carefully and treasured fiercely.
        It is a bond that you would not let go easily; you will defend it at all cost. It takes
        time to nurture a friendship. It is not created for the nonce. It is cultivated with much
        love and care over time. There is a great deal that goes into building and keeping a
        friendship. It is love and care that keep a friendship going. Where there is no love but
        only greed and selfishness there is no friendship at all.

        A friend is one who will sacrifice anything for you and yet not feel it a sacrifice at all,
        for there is love and concern for the other in a true friendship. When there is love in a
        friendship it can last a lifetime.

        A true friend is one who will share in your joys and in your troubles. Your friend will
        feel joy in your enjoyment and pain in your time of trouble. It is heart-warming and
        comforting to have a real friend. You know you will have a shoulder to weep on if sorrow or
        failure comes your way. Just as you will be assured of a hand to share a high five with in
        your joy and success. A friend is one who shares with you with no expectations. There is no
        quid pro quo in such a friendship. Friendship gives true happiness, because when you have
        a real friend you have all their love.
    </string>

    <string name="third_text">Sharing and caring characterize a real friendship. True friends share
        with each other and care for each other with all their heart. Anything of life can be
        shared by true friends. Whether it is life’s troubles and miseries, or joys and happiness
        or then life’s many surprises or events and occurrences.

        Friendship is all about love.

        A true friend is one who loves you and appreciates you as you are. There are neither any
        demands made of you nor any compulsions on you from your true friend. When friendship is
        all about love, it is a special place in your heart that you reserve for your friend, just
        as your friend keeps a special place for you in her/his heart.

        In a true friendship there is an unsaid mutuality and reciprocity. A friend is one you can
        be sure of. You have the assurance of a friend’s love and care at all times. And you in
        turn will always do anything to keep your friendship going strong.

        A true friend brightens your life

        Friends can make us chirpy when we are low and down. A true friend will do anything to make
        your sour face brighten up with cheer and smiles. A friend is one who will be your side when
        all others will part ways with you. Likewise, you will go out of your way to make your
        friend happy when trying times befall her or him.

        When friendship is true there is no need to showcase it or parade it. True friendship is
        shared at heart and it is reflected even in small ways, in word and deed. With a true
        friend the bonding and friendship grows from strength to strength. Even skirmishes and tiffs
        that may crop up between friends do not jeopardize their friendship if they are true friends
        who love each other deeply.

        Your real friend is one who may not praise you to your face, but will praise you at heart
        and thank God for the love and friendship she or he shares with you. Friendship between you
        and your true friend should be cherished and treasured. It is strong enough to last a
        lifetime.
    </string>

</resources>
